[Music]
hi it's Kourtney Kardashian
first I'm gonna start by doing my
morning skincare routine and then my
makeup look for when I do my own makeup
and I do really simple simple makeup so
I'm going to show you how I do that so
today we're doing a purifying mask and
this one is route science facial masks
and you mix it yourself this is a detox
purifying and clarifying mask ooh
so today I am mixing it with honey but
you can mix it with water you can mix it
with anything honey is also
antibacterial and full of antioxidants
okay then I'm using this brush it's very
sticky and it feels a little weird but
all for a good cause I try to use clean
beauty products as much as possible the
beauty reform laws have not been changed
in 80 years and it is sadly up to us as
consumers to try and figure out what is
safe and not safe which is why I love aw
geez app called skin deep where you can
tell what is safe and not safe I started
becoming obsessed with the products that
I put on my kids skin first and then I
started thinking about my own the mask
actually feels nice you know how some
masks really tighten up I just did this
crazy mask with Kamri so
that she forced me to do and my whole
face was pulling my eyeballs were pulled
down here where my whole eye was open
and I couldn't take it I don't like to
waste time so I I'm going to make my lip
scrub so I am mixing equal parts of
honey and coconut oil mixing it all
together and I just keep these products
in my bathroom so that I can make them
any time I love to do a lip scrub if
especially if I'm going to be wearing
like a bright lip or a dark lip to make
sure that your lips are really soft this
is the the raw sugar organic of course
and everything is organic I store it in
a little glass container like this but
I'm just showing you guys how to make it
okay then I take the scrub
[Music]
and it tastes yummy you can eat it while
I'm sitting here I'm gonna drink my
avocado smoothie so now I'm gonna wash
this mask off and the lip scrub and I
use a muslin cloth instead of a
washcloth okay so then I use these fresh
pads from a dermatologist Christie kid
that are just pretty natural they have
tea tree oil and witch hazel different
things they just keep my skin in check
Barbara storm hyaluronic serum is one of
my most favorite products I use it day
and night when I was drinking celery
juice oh it was making my whole body
feel dehydrated I will put this curly
beauty elixir spray you can use any
water spray though like and even you can
just use water if you want and then I'll
put a little oil it also give us a
little glow under your makeup then every
day I put on sunscreen whether it's
raining sunny I love the elta MD and
this is a new product that I'm just
started trying from them that has
hyaluronic acid inside of it I have not
worn sunscreen every day for my whole
life
I used to always be afraid of sunscreen
and would think that it would mean let
me break out and I put it on my hands
which is a trick that Chloe taught me
and I do this every day
no matter what
don't feel we're sipping my shake doing
my skincare is like a moment of the day
where I have to myself I think doing my
makeup is not something I look as
forward to because I love getting my
makeup done I'm so busy that I love to
sit and get other things done watch
edits of our show work on Poosh you know
have phone calls and so doing my own
makeup is more of a task which i think
is why I do this really quick makeup
routine one of the things I learned when
I was getting my skin in check was that
people would do my makeup and everyone
would use different foundations and so I
started making everyone used this
foundation that I love it's oxygen etics
and it's healthy for your skin and I mix
two colors honey and almond and I swear
that this is one of the things that
helped really get my skin together I
apply this with my hands I also do my
skin before my eyes because I don't
really when I do my own makeup I don't
really do eyes so I kind of do things a
little backwards
see other people do birds I think I told
Kendall about this too i think she uses
it i have been using this under eye
concealer forever
it's make up forever lift concealer and
I'm scared to check the score because I
just really love it and in living your
best life not every single thing can be
perfectly its boring well so we do our
best and then I use this mini Beauty
Blender just for under eyes I just kind
of sweep this all over my face and I do
not wear blush so I like to do a little
of it with bronzer we are keeping it
super simple so I use the same bronzer
to contour my nose my eyelids and bronze
my face and this is Kim's k'kaw Beauty
contour and instead of drawing the lines
on my face I like to keep it a little
more natural so I put it on my hand I
take a brush
this is if just I don't do this every
time I do my makeup this is like a once
in a while if you just want a little
extra this is to cover any little spots
and I'm not appreciating I have been
wearing makeup since eighth grade I
think I mean we didn't wear makeup to
school and get was for like parties or
on weekends we would wear a dark
lipstick some translucent powder this
one is Laura Mercier and I put my Beauty
Blender into it and I just go over the
spots that I don't want to be super
shiny little mascara and I always curl
my eyelashes first this is the choice
erat eyelash curler I'll watch my
sister's do makeup tutorials and I'm
like we do some makeup so differently
all of us this is my Lancome mascara
this is my name on it
mascara isn't really going you know into
your skin so to me I choose you like I
don't feel as guilty okay so I like to
over line this is a Kylie lip liner
Dolce K is the color and I love her lip
liners I think it's my favorite Kylie
product I use Kim and Kylie's lines for
different things I think it's amazing
how they both come up with such
different products both serving my
different makeup needs
[Music]
this is rms magic hour and i like the
line to be a bit darker than the
lipstick 90's vibes my daughter loves
makeup she has a little vanity in her
room that my mom gave her for Christmas
I let her play and I try to keep her
makeup as clean as possible filling in
my eyebrows I do it really I pretty much
stay with the shape I don't do any crazy
tricks or anything I just kind of fill
in a bit this is Luminizer sometimes I
will put the tiniest touch on the sides
just right here but I am NOT a fan of
the crazy like the contour the
highlighter like that whole look is not
my vibe that's it thank you for watching
I hope you learned something about
natural beauty bye guys
you